tweetbeat.com 2011-06-25

# Privacy Policy on Kosmix

Thank you for visiting kosmix.com or tweetbeat.com. These websites are now operated by Wal-Mart-Stores, Inc. (“Walmart”).

Please click here to see the [full Walmart privacy policy](http://walmartstores.com/9243.aspx).

This policy provides additional information specific to the Kosmix and Tweetbeat websites.

We collect personal information you provide, such as your name or e-mail address, to provide the services you request, to ensure proper operation of the websites, and to perform site analytics, and such other purposes that are consistent with the Walmart privacy policy.

This policy also governs how we provide online advertising on these websites. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect information when you visit this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this website, other websites, and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may also place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as pixel tags in connection with serving ads and/or collecting information about your visit to the website. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not receiving such advertisements, [click here.](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp)

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy or wish to exclude your personal information from such marketing communications, please tell us so at:

**Kosmix Corporation**   
444 Castro Street, Suite 109   
Mountain View, CA 94041   
ph: 650-938-2300   
fax: 650-938-5959   
email: [legal@kosmix.com](mailto:legal@kosmix.com)

You may also unsubscribe from our emails via the opt-out mechanism contained in those emails.

If you would like to update or delete your e-mail address, mailing address or other personal information please contact us the same way.

This policy was last updated: 5/2/2011.
